Curious about the fate
of the missing girl,
we stopped by Navarro Village
on our way back from home.
We heard Count Nardi,
the local lord, was suspicious,
so we snuck into his mansion
to look for the girl.
We successfully found
Miss Veronica, but...
the warehouse was attacked by bandits.
Don't worry, though.
We defeated the bad guys.
Prince Renato executed a beautiful
Number 38, settling the matter for now.
Always a Catch!
Knight Captain
Episode 8
The Secret Date of the One That Got Away
Can you tell what they're talking about?
No, I can't hear them.
The crown prince gives me the willies.
What's going to happen to us?
Th-Thank you so much for your help.
Because of you, we were
able to catch the bandits.
And I'm terribly sorry
for causing a disturbance.
You had a reason to "kidnap" her, right?
I'm just glad everyone's safe.
However, the fact remains that
I mobilized a number of my men.
I'm prepared to accept any punishment.
But...
Your Highness, you're not wrong,
but perhaps Lady Maria should
apologize for trespassing first.
Lord Raimondo!
You're right.
SHOCK
You, too?
You even had a weapon.
This is for self-defense.
And you knocked out helpless soldiers
as soon as you ran into them.
There was a reason for that.
What reason?
WAAAH
I'm sorry!
I'll do anything! Please forgive me!
Anything?
You just said you'd do anything,
didn't you?
What?
Raimondo, did you record that?
Yes, sir.
What does that mean? You're scaring me!
She didn't trespass.
My grandmother must've let
Lady Maria in through the window.
Lady Maria gave me the courage
to face the bandits.
I am grateful to her.
She has nothing to apologize for.
Thank you, Lord Hugo.
I see. In that case, we won't hold you
accountable for this disturbance.
And the matter with Count Vesentini, who
started all of this, has been resolved.
What? How do you know about that?
Allow me to explain.
First, the royal castle was informed
of the rash of bandit attacks
on the road to Navarro Village
and investigated.
We found that recently, Count Vesentini
had made a deal with Count Nardi
Vesentini
Villagers
Gives Crops
Marry my
daughter,
not a farmer!
I'll pay!
Give me all
your crops!
to purchase a large amount of crops.
What caught our attention was
why Count Vesentini was so
interested in these crops.
We discovered that the scent
compounds in this crop
match those of a certain item
that's currently available in Rubini.
What item?
A powerful hallucinogenic drug.
No...
The drug sells at a high price.
Count Vesentini must've wanted
his daughter to marry Hugo
so he could monopolize
the village's crops.
But without hard evidence, we couldn't
proceed with our investigation.
That's when the request to rescue
the kidnapped girl reached us,
and we brought our knights here.
His Highness didn't need to come,
but he insisted since we
might run into Lady Maria.
Anyway, the kidnapping was a surprise.
Wait.
I can't believe the village's crops
were being used for that.
It's true that they had a deal.
We've been questioning Count Nardi
and Count Vesentini about it.
My father is innocent.
He knew nothing about the drug.
Don't worry.
The crop is harmless
if the compounds aren't extracted
using a specialized process.
We didn't find such
processing equipment here.
Your father will be allowed to
return in a few days.
Good.
I appreciate you looking out
for Mimi. Thank you.
So the villagers won't be punished. Great.
Everything is not great.
I hope you're very sorry for
what you've done, Lady Maria.
Why am I the only one in trouble?
Hey, stop pushing! Careful!
What? You're trespassing!
Should you be saying that, Lady Maria?
Sorry for breaking in,
but we're just so glad.
What a relief.
It's great news.
I'm sorry for making all of you worry.
I'm sorry for leaving
without saying anything.
I'll be sure to talk to my father.
Good idea.
As the future lord,
I'll do everything I can
for Navarro Village and Veronica.
They're overcoming obstacles
together, hand in hand!
I love it!
They have my eternal support!
Mimi, calm down.
You heard that?
Veronica.
Dad...
Does that make you the
chief of Navarro Village?
The others told me what happened.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Come on, Veronica.
Yes, Dad.
This feels like an awkward
father-daughter relationship.
Oh, I recognize this.
It doesn't begin to make up for it,
but may I treat you to a meal at my home?
Veronica, you're back.
Auntie.
Sorry for making you worry.
So good.
Bread made with spices
and dried fruit, huh?
All these dishes use
this village's spices.
This is good. Very good.
All of this is delicious.
You could open a restaurant, sir.
I'm glad you like it.
You're a great cook.
My father's always been a good cook.
Trying to make the most of the village's
spices made me better at cooking.
You have great culinary sense.
I agree. This is delicious.
But if dishes made with
these spices are this good,
shouldn't they be famous and
the village more developed?
Veronica, I'm sorry!
I opposed your marriage
despite knowing how you felt.
I thought Lord Hugo marrying
Count Vesentini's daughter
would be better for the village.
Please forgive me for not
putting your happiness first.
I'm sorry for not discussing
anything with you, too.
Um, may I say something?
In times like these, you'll
feel better if you let it all out.
That's your specialty.
"If fists won't work, ask,"
is an Annovazzi family motto.
I love this village.
I love how warm and helpful everyone is,
so I've always wanted to
make life easier here.
Hugo and I planned to return
to the village eventually.
What?
What? Then... you weren't eloping?
You jumped to conclusions?
Don't worry about it, milady.
Hugo is a kind man
who cares for the village.
I believed that together,
we could carve a new path.
I left the village so we
could see the rest of the world
and bring back new ideas.
We planned to look for ways to process
this village's crops into something else
or other crops suited to the land.
So please, Dad.
Let me marry Hugo.
I want to do what I can for this
village while supporting him.
Please.
I thought you were still just a child.
It's pathetic, but only after
you went missing did I realize
I wanted you to be happy
more than anything.
Then...
But it's not so simple, Veronica.
Yes, Dad.
Lord Hugo, please look after Veronica.
I will.
We'll take our leave and go.
Lord Hugo, can we count on you
to handle the aftermath?
Yes, sir.
Good luck, Miss Veronica.
Thank you so much, Lady Maria.
If you ever find yourself in the
royal capital, come see Mimi.
SHAKE SHAKE
You're welcome anytime!
Wear matching outfits!
Yes, milady.
I don't know about that,
but I promise we'll visit.
Lord Hugo, I'll have my family
send you a whole roast cow.
A whole roast cow?
Prince Renato.
Please, milord.
Look after Lady Maria.
I will.
Thanks for coming this far.
Give my best to everyone back home.
Lady Mimi!
Thank you!
See you later!
It's beautiful.
What a lovely city.
This place is small, but
it's a famous tourist spot.
Mimi.
Shall we look around town together?
I-Is that...
a secret date?!
Always a Catch!
Your Highness...
Let's forget our titles for a while
and enjoy ourselves.
GLOW
He's not hiding anything at all!
The princely aura pouring
out of him is too bright!
He's a genuine royal born and bred!
The guards will follow behind us,
but I've put on a disguise.
Now no one will notice
I'm a crown prince.
No, this is totally obvious.
His Highness believes his disguise is perfect, so please go along with it
What...
I'm not sure I can.
Hey, buddy.
I've got a wish-granting lamp.
Your friends back home will love it.
Your High—oops!
His cover will be blown
if I call him His Highness.
Y-You might like to check
out the shops over there.
Mimi?
If you see anything you'd like,
I'll buy it for you.
Don't waste your money on me.
If it happened to break
while I was doing anything...
Let's go this way next.
Look. There's a bear here.
That's the owner of a handicrafts shop.
Oh, no. How embarrassing.
GLARE
Nice. We lost the guys following us.
Mimi, are you tired?
Should we sit and rest a while?
No, I'm totally fine.
What's that?
It's a festival.
Let's have some fun, Mimi.
What? But...
Nice shot. Did you
learn to shoot somewhere?
No.
This looks so good.
Mimi, don't let it escape!
These are this region's specialty.
How cute.
Hooray!
Good for you.
Wrong target!
Th-That's against the rules, Mimi.
You're more playful than usual today.
Am I?
Something smells good.
Welcome.
BLUSH
What's this?
Grilled squid. Have you heard of it?
I've never had it.
Oh, right. Muro has no seas.
Care to try it?
GLOW
The sweet and salty sauce
and plump squid are delicious.
Your Highness, try some.
It's good.
Right?
It's actually my first time
walking around town like this.
I thought so. It's hard for someone
in your position to enjoy a festival.
Yes. I had fun spending time with you.
Oh, no. I'm so clumsy.
I'll go get a damp handkerchief.
Wait here.
No, I'll go.
It's fine. Wait here.
We'll be with His Highness
He insisted I wait here.
I never imagined I'd ever
be escorted like this.
BLUSH
Oh? Are you all alone, miss?
Wanna hang with me?
Hey, girl, hey.
HEY
Wait a minute...
Are you actually hitting on me?
You must not have gotten
any attention before.
Whatever. You're a tourist, right?
HEY
There's a spot nearby where we can chill.
Chill?
Why don't we party together?
Do you have business with my companion?
AUGH
Y-Y-Y-You're not by yourself?
Sorry about that!
You snuck up behind someone again.
This town is lively, but
its alleys aren't the safest.
I must get the local lord to handle it.
You knew from the start, didn't you?
Yes.
Yet you seemed unbothered by it.
All my subjects are important to me,
no matter who they are.
You're right.
Someday they'll be my people, too.
Mimi, about that...
I'd like to speak in private.
Shall we walk?
Prince Renato, will we
be safe without guards?
I guess I'll be with you.
You're so dependable.
Where do you keep such strength
in your slender arms?
I could say the same about you.
I'm sorry for putting you in danger.
Not at all. I'm the one
who stuck my nose into it.
You have nothing to apologize for.
Mimi,
as crown princess, your life
will always be in danger.
You'll always be escorted by guards,
and your food must be tasted for poison.
You'll bear the hopes of the people
and great responsibility.
In one month, a party will be
held at the royal palace.
I plan to announce our engagement
to the kingdom there.
Not everyone will approve.
Some will criticize you.
After calling off my
engagement to Lady Aida,
there's no taking this one back
after going public.
So this is your last chance
to decline my proposal.
What? What?
What are you talking about?
I wouldn't visit your family
if I didn't intend to marry you.
I wouldn't have tea with the queen.
I wouldn't spend six days traveling
to tell my family about it.
Mimi?
I wouldn't ask Aida to teach me
to be a crown princess.
I wouldn't have trained to become a lady.
Compared to the ladies who have
worked so hard to marry you,
I'm an utter failure.
I'll do everything I can, of course.
But I'm still a long way away
from being a proper crown princess.
But since coming to this kingdom,
SWIPE
I've felt lots of new feelings,
like the ones I have for you.
I'm truly glad I met you.
I want to marry you.
I see. You'll marry me?
That's what I said.
I'm so happy, Mimi.
Premarital relations are forbidden.
Step away from each other.
How long have you been here?
From the start.
You absolutely were not!
It's time to go.
Aw.
No complaining.
But...
You weren't there.
He wasn't, right?
You totally weren't.
To Be Continued
Translation: Sho Stifler
Timing: Mariana Martinez
Editing: Alicia Ashby
Quality Control: Ashley Barboza
Final Quality Control: Michelle Tymon
I thought friends fought but
ultimately resolved their differences
with their fists and made up,
but I was wrong.
I'm shocked to learn some
friends don't fight at all.
Next Time
The One Who Got Away Plays Cupid
Oops, I spoke my mind again.